lrmonline.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy + Terms | lrmonline

## Privacy Policy

### Effective: April 14, 2016

Latino Review LLC is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining a safe online experience for all of our users and customers while providing a quality user experience. Because we gather certain types of information about and from you, our users, in order to fulfill your requests and better serve your needs, you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of this information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, how to correct or change it, and what steps we take to safeguard personal information provided to us online. Please read the complete Privacy Policy below, as well as our User Agreement, and contact us if you have any questions.

### Cookies

We use third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our Web site in order to provide advertisements on our Web site, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. They may also use this information to track the effectiveness of those ads. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please go to http://www.net- workadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp ([http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp\))

**Links** : Be aware that when you click on ad banners, you may be redirected to other sites not operated by Latino Review LLC. You are responsible for information that you provide to these sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that requests personal information. Note that this policy does not cover the privacy practices of these linked sites.

**General Information Collected** : When visiting our site, some general information is collected including: IP address (your computer’s unique signature) Operating system (e.g., Windows 95) Browser software (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape) Internet Service Provider (e.g., AT&T, Verizon).

The information we collect is aggregated to reflect the population as a whole rather than focused on individuals. We use it to help us better understand the people who visit our Web Site and to continually improve our services. In addition, like many other sites with paid advertising, we disclose some of this non- personally identifiable, aggregate information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and clicked on their advertisements.

### Third Party Service Providers

Latino Review LLC does not collect any personal information other than your email address should you desire to receive our Daily Newsletter.  Agents and Partners of Latino Review, LLC may occasionally process individual user data as required to provide services for which the user has registered. However, they are not allowed to use this information for any other purpose. All individual user data is owned and controlled by Latino Review, LLC.  From time to time we may partner with third party service providers to offer additional products and services within the Web Site. To participate in these offerings, you may be asked to provide personal information and agree to terms and conditions relating to the third party service provider. Such requests for information will be displayed and requested by the third party in a straightforward manner with explanation as to whose privacy statement governs the collection of such information.

### Personal Information

It is the responsibility of each user to provide Latino Review LLC with accurate information at all times. Latino Review LLC currently does not collect any personal information such as name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, age, or gender.  The only information that you are asked to provide should you desire to receive our newsletter is your email address.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with best practices employed by other publishers and regulatory organizations across the industry. We recommend that you check the Privacy Policy when you visit our Web Site to be sure that you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy, or in how we use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make any retroactive material changes in how we handle previously collected personal information unless you allow us to do so, or unless we are legally required to do so, and in such a case we will e-mail registered Web Site visitors information on material changes to this Privacy Policy.

### Questions?

For any questions or comments concerning Latino Review LLC’s privacy policy, please write to:

**Latino Review LLC**

3060 Peachtree Road

Suite 380

Atlanta, GA 30305

© Copyright 2016 Latino Review LLC, Latino-Review and the LRM logos are trademarks of Latino Review LLC.
